<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports Blog on Jordan Saadeh Sports Analytics Blog</title>
    <link>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/categories/sports-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports Blog on Jordan Saadeh Sports Analytics Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jordansaadeh.github.io/categories/sports-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Which Minnesota Vikings Wide Receiver Had the Best Rookie Season?</title>
      <link>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/2021/04/25/which-minnesota-vikings-wide-receiver-had-the-best-rookie-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/2021/04/25/which-minnesota-vikings-wide-receiver-had-the-best-rookie-season/</guid>
      <description>If you are as big as a Minnesota Vikings fan as I am, you would know that the Vikings have had their fair share of talented wide receivers in the past. From Hall of Famer Cris Carter to Justin Jefferson who is entering his second season in the league. For this project I wanted to look at three different Viking receivers and compare who each of their rookie seasons by looking at three main statistics: receptions, receiving yards, and touchdowns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are the New England Patriots more of a passing threat with Cam Newton or Tom Brady?</title>
      <link>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/2021/04/04/are-the-new-england-patriots-more-of-a-passing-threat-with-cam-newton-or-tom-brady/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/2021/04/04/are-the-new-england-patriots-more-of-a-passing-threat-with-cam-newton-or-tom-brady/</guid>
      <description>All good things must come to an end, and that is what happened in the summer going into the 2020 NFL season with the New England Patriots quarterback for the past two decades, Tom Brady. After 20 seasons with the Patriots, Brady was able to give the city of New England six Super Bowl Championships, 13 AFC Championship games, while winning three the NFL MVP awards and Super Bowl MVP three times.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
