<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Jordan Saadeh Sports Analytics Blog</title>
    <link>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/categories/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Jordan Saadeh Sports Analytics Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jordansaadeh.github.io/categories/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are the New England Patriots More of a Passing Threat with Brady or Newton?</title>
      <link>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/2021/04/04/are-the-new-england-patriots-more-of-a-passing-threat-with-brady-or-newton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/2021/04/04/are-the-new-england-patriots-more-of-a-passing-threat-with-brady-or-newton/</guid>
      <description>All good things must come to an end, and that is what happened in the summer going into the 2020 NFL season with the New England Patriots quarterback for the past two decades, Tom Brady. After 20 seasons with the Patriots, Brady was able to give the city of New England six Super Bowl Championships, 13 AFC Championship games, while winning three the NFL MVP award and Super Bowl MVP three times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Saadeh Sports Blog</title>
      <link>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/2021/03/15/jordan-saadeh-sports-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jordansaadeh.github.io/2021/03/15/jordan-saadeh-sports-blog/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my first blog post, I hope you’re as excited as I am as I document my thoughts, questions, and answers to those questions. I will as well be giving updates on my project that I will be working on, whether that is of I think found some fascinating that I never knew and want to share or anything else in that matter. The first question I look forward to answering in my first project is: Why the New England Patriots need Tom Brady at quarterback to win a Super Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
